(Sheldon:)I didn't hog anything.
(Sheldon:)Unlike you and that weird
lasagna with raisins in it.
(Leonard:)You want some of this?
(Leonard:)I'll give you some.
BERNADETTE: Hey!
(Bernadette:)Sheldon, Leonard,
living room, right now!
She said my name first;
that must kill you.
BERNADETTE: I don't know
what you think you're doing,
(Bernadette(off):)but this is a very difficult
time for my husband!
(Bernadette(off):)We're eating the last food
his mother ever made,
(Bernadette(off):)and you were gonna throw it
at each other like children?!
(Bernadette(off):)Whatever it is you're
fighting about, put it aside,
(Bernadette(off):)go back in there
and be a good friend to Howard
(Bernadette(off):)or there's no dessert
for either of you!
(Bernadette(off):)Look at me
when I'm talking to you!
(Bernadette(off):)And don't think...
(Howard:)You guys ever notice sometimes
Bernadette sounds like my mom?
(Amy:)I don't hear it.
No, not at all.
(all groaning quietly)